

Zakaria Bin Zainuddin

Web Developer

Self-taught programmer whose has been dedicated day and night studying in order to be a great programmer. Outgoing and enthusiastic employee with great adaptability in various working environments. Passionate at learning and can lead people in a team.

CONTACT

- zakariazainuddin41@ gmail.com
- 013-9213678
- Pekan,Pahang
- https://zakariazainuddin. netlify.app/
- in linkedin.com/in/zakariazainuddin-7a5744236
- zacky791 (Zakaria) (github.com)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript (ES6)
- React
- Tailwind Css

INTEREST





Chess



REFERENCES

Ts. Dr. Muhammad Fakhrul Bin Yusuf

Senior Lecturer Contact:mfakhrul@ump. edu.my/094245000

Muhammad Figree

Quality Engineer Contact: 0192234491

WORK EXPERIENCE

QUALITY ENGINEER

ZF Friedrichshafen | Jan 2022 to Jun 2022

- Collaboration with Germany engineer regarding mega project that's involved of standard operation procedure (SOP), installation new tools for new model Mercedes (W206, S580, GLCX200)
- Monitoring Statical Process Control (SPC) by performing Process Capability Index (CPK) and Machine Capability Index (CMK) to every tool inside factory
- Manage meeting with cross functional teams to solve regarding quality issues by using the 8D reports until the case officially closed

ASSISTANT PRODUCTION ENGINEER

Isuzu | Feb 2021 to Aug 2021

- Assist project planning on changing new version model of D-max from arriving 16 new jig until to the final testing line
- Changed assembly parts guideline from Assembly of sheet (AOS) to new Standard operation procedure (SOP)
- Presented to higher management on punch list and cycle time that has been recorded and calculated
- Increased 18% efficiency by proposing to reduce cycle time at every station

COURSES & TRAINING

Udemy

- Build Responsive Real-World Websites with HTML and CSS
- The Complete JavaScript Course 2023: From Zero to Expert!
- React The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux)

EDUCATION

University Malaysia Pahang (UMP)

2017 - 2021

 Bachelor of Industrial Technology Management (Hons) CGPA 3.20

College Matriculation Pahang (KMPH)

2016 - 2017

• Study Computer Science, Biology, Chemistry and Add Math